This is Ranma from the Saotome
School of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
Let go.
And this is Akane, who comes
from the Tendo Dojo.
What are you doing?
They were joined
in an arranged betrothal by their parents.
- Hmm.
- Don't tell me what to do.
Pain in the butt.
As it turns out, Ranma has a unique issue.
What the hell are you doing?
Every time he gets splashed
with cold water, he turns into a girl.
RANMA1/2
What about school?
I've decided that we're moving
into the dojo with them for a while.
I HATE MEN!
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
You get to go to school with me and Akane.
See you there in a bit.
Wait for me, Nabiki.
- I wanna leave with--
- What are you saying?
You're engaged now
and Ranma's right there.
You've gotta make sure
he gets to school okay.
And walking to school with you is kinda
annoying, gotta be honest.
Hmm.
Let me make one thing clear.
The two of us don't know each other.
You don't gotta tell me twice.
I don't want you acting all friendly
with me at school.
Like hell I'd freaking do that.
It's not like I really give much of a crap
about bratty-ass tomboys like you.
If I'm being honest, I hate them
more than anyth--
The hell was that, you old fart?
You are not the kind of guy who's going to
have the luxury of choosing a girl.
Listen, Ranma.
I'll only say this once...
Hmm.
Oh, what's the matter, Dad?
Tell us that you're okay if you can.
- Wanna fight?
- Oh, come on.
Whoa! A cat's crab-walking.
Huh.
Get outta here!
Hmm. Ha!
Serves you right!
What are you doing?
- Going home.
- Wait a second.
I won't be long.
I'm just taking a quick bath.
You'll be late for school though.
Do you really think I can go to school
in my girl form?
Honestly.
It'll only take some hot water
to turn you back into a boy, right?
OSTEOPATHIC CLINIC -
CHIROPRACTOR
ACUPUNCTURE - ACUPRESSURE
...and that's the whole story.
Hot water? Just a minute, Akane.
Thank you so much.
An acquaintance?
I guess I got nothing
but bad luck this morning.
Real pain in the butt.
Um.
Ah, hello. Apologies.
You don't have to be scared of her.
This is my skeletal specimen, Betty.
Huh?
Hmm.
Ranma, the water.
How are you, Akane?
Ah. Dr. Tofu.
Hmm?
- Hope it's a good morning.
- Good morning.
Mmm?
I haven't seen you lately.
You haven't been injured?
Not at all.
I mean, I don't do anything
that would cause an injury.
It's not just me though.
You've seemed busy too, Dr. Tofu.
Yeah...
Aha.
So who was that guy?
Dr. Tofu's a chiropractor.
Very skilled doctor.
He's strong too, isn't he?
Oh! So you can tell?
He managed to sneak up on me.
It's like he erased his presence.
You wouldn't think that about him
at first, would you?
Ever since I was a little kid,
I'd always come in to see him
every time I had an injury.
Mm-hmm?
Hey. That guy looked like a man.
What?
It's just that you said yesterday
that you hated every man.
I do.
Oh, boy. I really hate...
Akane Tendo is coming.
FURINKAN HIGH SCHOOL
- Huh?
- ...all these guys!
- Akane Tendo!
- You're not gonna get to school!
We've got our eyes on you!
- You need to get out of here.
- Huh?
Ooh!
Out of the way. I'm gonna be late.
Oh, please marry me!
Hyah!
Tend--
I can stop you by for--
I'll defeat you
before any of these other guys!
Hyah!
Every morning seems pretty rough
for your little sister, Nabiki.
Ranma's here too.
Ranma!
Why don't you come in the building?
What about her?
Akane can
totally take care of herself.
Whoa.
Hmm?
Ugh.
This whole group of guys is so annoying!
- Honestly.
- Hmm?
They're so unsophisticated.
It appears
their many attempts to defeat you
are in the hopes that they have the chance
to ask for your hand.
Uh. Yes, I'm well aware, Kuno.
Good morning.
Hmm?
The first bell of the day will be ringing
soon enough.
So, let me challenge you beforehand.
You're surprisingly popular.
Stay out of this. Or you'll get hurt.
What exactly is going on here?
What do you mean?
Hey, you there.
Huh? What do you want?
Your attitude toward Akane is impudent.
Well that's 'cause...
- You know?
- No, can't say that I do.
You! Identify yourself now.
- Ran--
- I suppose it's proper etiquette
to state my name before asking for others.
Fine! I'll introduce myself.
- Mmm, uh, go ahead.
- Very well.
I am Tatewaki Kuno from class E.
Kendo club captain, undefeated champion
and a new rising star
in the high school kendo world,
also known as
Furinkan High School's
Crack of Blue Thunder!
Did he just say "The Blue Thunder"?
You heard of that?
Can't say I have.
Oh, is it my turn now?
- I'm staying at the Tendo Dojo.
- Ah.
Hold on. What did I just hear you say?
Huh? It's a temporary thing...
- What?
- ...staying with the Tendos.
You bastard!
I'm from the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
You get to live under the same roof
as my precious Akane?
- Hold this.
- Hey!
A challenge, huh?
Ranma Saotome accepts.
Look. Is somebody fighting
against Kuno?
Well, their funeral.
Your unruly behavior
has been bothering Akane.
Defeat will come
at the hands of Tatewaki Kuno!
I'm not the one
that's hounding her!
He's only staying with us
as a tenant.
I will not debate this!
Listen.
You didn't hear me
the first time I said it.
Wow. He closed the gap
in the blink of an eye.
There is nothing between us
and there is not a single part of me
that has any interest in Akane whatsoever.
Ugh. He's actually competent?
I mean, really.
She's stubborn, violent, obstinate
and is always pouting
which makes her so ugly.
I'd be more than happy
to let you have her--
Shut up, pervert!
Don't call me that!
How dare you slander Akane like this!
Unacceptable!
Is that his dad?
Kuno got beat by a panda!
- A strong one at that.
- What just happened?
PE EQUIPMENT
This freaking sucks.
I would've beaten his ass
if it hadn't started raining.
Mmm, you know,
I wonder about that.
What do you want?
Take a look at your neck.
A bruise?
Must've been then.
He didn't touch me
so that's pretty impressive.
He would've blasted
a hole in you if he did.
Best case scenario? It'd be a draw.
You really think so?
Hmm.
BUFOON
Gotta admit, that's impressive.
You have no idea when he touched you?
Ranma Saotome,
I believed you to be
more competent than that.
This has a spelling error!
- You spell "idiot" this way.
- No, you don't.
BUFFOO
Please know how deeply I hate you.
I'm so flattered.
So, to make a long story short,
Saotome here had been studying abroad
in China up until recently.
Well, now that introductions are
taken care of,
- Miss Akane Tendo.
- Mm-hmm?
I want both of you out standing
in the corridor for coming in late.
All of this is your fault.
I was the one who got pulled
into fighting your boyfriend.
I'm not saying this to brag, but I
take care of them every morning by myself.
Why were all of them so riled up anyway?
That's all because of Kuno.
Excuse me?
Anyone who desires a chance
with Akane must defeat her!
I will not accept anyone else's attempt
to try and earn her hand!
- So, yeah.
- I see.
What did you say?
They're already engaged?
Yep.
They got put into an arranged marriage
situation by their parents.
Damn it all! I warned you, Ranma!
Kuno? Go stand in the corridor.
What are you? Superman?
I won't forgive you!
So you fight Kuno and those other guys
every morning?
Yep. And none of them have managed
to beat me yet.
Well, no way for him to get better
if he's only fighting girls.
You best watch your mouth.
You asking me to beat you up next?
Ah, I'm good.
You may be violent and feral,
but you're still a girl.
- I can't seriously fight against a girl--
- Oh!
What?
If you put it like that,
I'm sure we can find a way
to have a match that's girl-on-girl.
Whoa!
Ranma Saotome, you savage.
What the hell was that?
Huh? Kuno?
I heard about your engagement to Akane.
What, now?
I will never bring myself to accept this!
Uh.
Hold up! Did I just hear you're engaged?
So every time you said you hated men,
were you just kidding?
Now hang on a second.
None of this is true.
Our parents are just doing
whatever they wa--
This the Furinkan High School Radio Club.
We wanna hear all about your engagement.
- Who are you?
- Cut it out!
...listeners are waiting
on the edge of their seats for more.
They wanna know about the thief
who stole Akane's heart.
I told you, the two of us are
getting forced into it by our parents.
You're running? You coward.
We're not going to be able to have
a decent fight in the hallway. Follow me!
Very well.
Man, this is fun!
So, are you gonna go on a date
with whoever wins the fight?
- Huh?
In a few words,
tell us how you're feeling.
Leave me alone!
Enough, you two! No running in the hall!
Why don't we try taking a shortcut?
Fine.
Both of them have jumped
out of the window!
- And listeners, we're on the third floor!
- Oh.
How are you feeling
right now?
I'm just fine.
Our fighters are going to fall
straight into the pool below.
- Well that's a relief.
- Idiot!
Oh, shit!
Wow, that was a big splash.
- Loud, too.
- That was crazy!
Look, I see Kuno!
What happened?
But where's Saotome? He good?
This is bad. I gotta go. Gotta go now!
Jeez. What a pain in my butt.
Oh, look. He's started moving.
He's swimming kind of funny.
Looks real creepy.
- Saotome...
- Uh?
...fight me.
Does he know?
Where did Saotome go?
- Fight me...
- Let go of me! Hey!
Get your freaking hands off me,
you giant asshole!
Oh?
Go to hell!
Whoa, there he goes! He escaped the fight.
Ranma Saotome ducked off like a rabbit...!
Hey, did Ranma's body
look different to you?
Yeah, he did look smaller.
That was surely a young maiden's body.
That can only mean...
Hear me, Ranma Saotome! You are a coward!
Damn it.
Ugh. Why did that bastard Kuno
have to squeeze my boob like that?
I can still feel it and it's gross.
I guess that's him finding out
my true identity.
- You're such a moron.
- Hmm?
What's your issue, Akane?
I wanted to make sure
that you knew you were stupid.
Jumping into the pool was not a good idea.
That's enough outta you!
You came to find me
just so you could tell me that?
You're the one who's an idiot.
Really? Good to know you feel that way.
I'll find something else
to use this hot water on.
Huh! Y-you got water?
You're being such a jerk!
- Saotome!
- Mmm?
It's Kuno.
Where did you go, Ranma Saotome?
- Heads up.
- Huh, what?
Hmm?
I'm challenging you, Kuno.
Wow. Akane. Do you mean it?
I'm flattered you'd approach me
to proposition a challenge.
Good. Very well.
If you win, I'll go on a date with you.
I'll give it my all but I hope to lose.
At no point did I ask you
to go out with me!
Hurry up and change back into a boy
while I'm stalling for time.
Ranma.
Now what the heck
am I supposed to do?
Oh.
Huh?
I saw you earlier.
Really? Why are you still in that form?
What was I supposed to do?
Hey. You haven't seen a weird guy
with a rattail, have you?
Mm-mmm, mm-mmm.
He's such a coward.
Running away in the middle of our fight.
My strength must've frightened him
to his core.
No real man would ever be that scared.
Pathetic! Unmanly!
Hmm.
I heard everything
while you were running your mouth.
Dropping me really hurt.
I would never run away or hide from you.
If you want it that bad,
I'll beat you up no matter where we are.
Bring it.
Mmm.
Interesting.
Okay. You'll be the one I go out with
if you win.
Neither one of us wants
to go out with you!
She's so strong.
She's an equal to Akane.
No. She might be even stronger.
Ha!
I'll tell you right now.
Ranma Saotome is
way stronger than I am.
Well, we should start heading home.
We're still in the middle
of school. The first class isn't over yet.
Oh, really? Well...
- Who on earth is that girl?
- You're gonna get us in trouble.
Ranma, you know, I heard
that you were causing a lot of issues
with Akane at school today.
That's 'cause she was trying to help me
when I never asked.
I don't know. I think
you're making a big deal out of nothing.
What's the big issue? Who cares
if a boy transforms into a girl?
Yeah, right. You can try and claim
that it might not matter much to you.
But have you considered
that I'm supposed to be his fiancée,
so it might actually affect me?
I don't like the idea of people assuming
I partnered up with a pervert
who can't even check to make sure
the bath is empty before going in.
Whatever. Not like I wanted
to thank her anyway.
Really?
Yeah, totally, I know her.
Girl in the Chinese shirt
with the little braid?
You do? You're telling the truth
and not some sort of joke?
Yep.
Uh, Kuno?
If you believe you have the ability
to keep beating me,
you couldn't be more wrong.
Just you wait and see.
This is for you.
TO THE PIGTAILED GIRL
Kuno wrote this for me?
Well, to the girl version of you, yeah.
I don't think he's put together
that you're the same person yet.
"I want to see you
Sunday morning at 10:00 a.m.
Come show yourself to me on the second
ground of Furinkan High School."
A challenge letter?
Kuno must be pretty competitive.
He's definitely persistent at least.
This is for real?
This guy's a pain in the rear.
Thank you for coming. It's appreciated.
I guess you didn't learn your lesson
the first time.
Huh? Where did
that wooden sword of yours go?
Huh. I have no need of it anymore.
Oh? You're sounding confident about that.
Now, my pigtailed girl.
I must confess,
I need to give you something!
Take this!
Uh.
I'm in love.
Hmm?
Please. No...